Guide to the Stanford University, Libraries, Department of Special Collections and University Archives, Records SC0756
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Exhibits Department Records, 1969-2010; Accession ARCH_2010_056; 32 Linear Feet; (22 boxes)
  - African Maps: Publicity (2004) (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - African Maps: Requests for display images (2004) (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - African Maps: Sample case titles, texts of repros. (2004) (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - African Maps: Stack Books checked out (2004) (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - African Maps: Text (2004) (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - African Maps: URL Transfer of Digital Files (2004) (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Ira Nowinski: The Photographer as Witness (August 15 -- November 30, 2004) (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Nowinski: Announcement and Invitation (2004) (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Nowinski: Case Maps (2004) (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Nowinski: Case 1 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Nowinski: Case 2 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Nowinski: Case 3 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Nowinski: Case 4 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Nowinski: Case 5 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Nowinski: Case 6 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Nowinski: Case 7 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Nowinski: Case 8 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Nowinski: Case 9 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Nowinski: Case 10 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Nowinski: Case 11 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Nowinski: Case 12 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Nowinski: Case 13 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Nowinski: Case 14 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Nowinski: Case 15 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Nowinski: Case 16 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Nowinski: Case 17 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Nowinski: Case 18 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Nowinski: Case 19 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Nowinski: Case 20 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Nowinski: Case 21 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Nowinski: Case 22 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Nowinski: Case 23 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Nowinski: Case 24 (2004) (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Nowinski: Catalog Binding Troubles (2004) (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Nowinski: Catalog Design Trials (2004) (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Nowinski: Catalog Display Copies (2004) (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Nowinski: Catalog Files sent to Stinehour Press (2004) (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Nowinski: Catalog Mockup (2004) (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Nowinski: Catalog -- Numbered set of images (2004) (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Nowinski: Catalog printing estimate (2004) (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Nowinski: Catalog Production/Proofs (2004) (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Nowinski: Catalog -- Statement for Stinehour Press/Sappi Paper Award (2004) (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Nowinski: Catalog -- unbound copies (2004) (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Nowinski: Duotone Colors (2004) (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Nowinski: Enlarged Print Captions (binder) (2004) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Nowinski: Jpegs (2004) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Nowinski: Negatives, Loan Agreements, and List of Prints for Reproduction (2004) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Nowinski: Press Check Exp. Reimbursement (2004) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Nowinski: Prints (2004) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Nowinski: Publicity Images (2004) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Nowinski: Reception (2004) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Nowinski: Sample Case Titles and Texts (2004) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Nowinski: Sign and Banners (2004) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Nowinski: Texts and Labels (2004) (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Secular Yiddish Schools (December 2004) (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Yiddish: Additional Subjects of Activities (2004) (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Yiddish: "Continuity" Case (2004) (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Yiddish: Curriculum Enrichment (2004) (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Yiddish: Email/Gella, Faxes too (2004) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Yiddish: Holocaust/Destruction of Jewish Life in Europe (2004) (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Yiddish: Labels (2004) (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Yiddish: Land of Israel; state (2004) (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Yiddish: Mounted Song Facsimiles (2004) (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Yiddish: Poster (2004) (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Yiddish: Texts (2004) (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Yiddish: Texts and Labels (2004) (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Facets of French History: Resources for Research in the Stanford University Libraries (March 17-June 12, 2005) Case Maps and Prep Sheets (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - French History: Colors (2005) (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - French History: Facsimiles (2005) (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - French History: Facsimile stats (2005) (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - French History: Floor Plan and Layouts (2005) (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - French History: Facets of French History/The Pleasures of Edo-Period Books joint guestbook (2005) (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - French History: Hoover Loan (2005) (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - French History: Keepsake (2005) (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - French History: Large Text Prints and Captions (2005) (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - French History: Miscellaneous Graphics (2005) (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - French History: Postcard (2005) (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - French History: Prep Flags (2005) (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - French History: Prep Sheets (2005) (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - French History: Production Schedule (2005) (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - French History: Publicity (2005) (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - The Pleasures of Edo-Period Books (2005) Case Books (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Japan Books: Colors (2005) (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Japan Books: Correspondence and Meeting Notes (2005) (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Japan Books: Fliers (2005) (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Japan Books: invitations (2005) (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Japan Books: Loan List (2005) (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Japan Books: Party Invitations (2005) (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Japan Books: Poster (2005) (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Japan Books: Texts and Labels (2005) (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - The Rise and Fall of the Slide Rule: 350 Years of Mathematical Calculators (June 30 -- October 9, 2005) (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Slide Rule: Backdrops and Banners (2005) (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Slide Rule: Booklet (2005) (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Slide Rule: Colors (2005) (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Slide Rule: Floorplan and Casemaps (2005) (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Slide Rule: Duplicate Lists (2005) (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Slide Rule: Graphic Requests (2005) (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Slide Rule: Guestbook (2005) (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Slide Rule: "How to Use a Slide Rule" (2005) (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Slide Rule: Loan Forms/Risk Management (2005) (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Slide Rule: LogLog Text (2005) (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Slide Rule: Debbie Douglas/Slide Rules MIT (2005) (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Slide Rule: Permissions (2005) (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Slide Rule: Postcard (2005) (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Slide Rule: Preliminary Outline (2005) (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Slide Rule: Press Release (2005) (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Slide Rule: Production Schedule (2005) (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Slide Rule: Text (2005) (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Slide Rule: Tom Wyman (2005) (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Herbert Matter: Modernist Photography and Graphic Design (October 20, 2005 -- February 11, 2006) Announcement Mailing (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Matter: Announcement and Reception Invitation (2005) (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Matter: Banner, preliminary designs (2005) (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Matter: Case Maps (2005) (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Matter: Catalog File Copy (2005) (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Matter: Catalog Mockups (2005) (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Matter: Catalog Proofs (2005) (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Matter: Central Banner (2005) (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Matter: Colors (2005) (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Matter: Early Planning Notes (2005) (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Matter: VAS/Filmstrip Scans (2005) (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Matter: Invoices (2005) (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Matter: Item Prep Sheets (2005) (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Matter: John Hill Visit (2005) (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Matter: LightJet Panels (2005) (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Matter: Offprints and Info (2005) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Matter: Production Schedule (2005) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Matter: Publicity (2005) (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Matter: Reveal Panels (2005) (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Matter: Rotunda Banner (2005) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Matter: Catalog Sales Panel and Info (2005) (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Matter: Sign (2005) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Matter: Text Drafts (2005) (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Matter: Text and Title Formats (2005) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Matter: Vanessa's Files (2005) (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Matter: Work Req for Banner Installation (2005) (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - The Earthquake of 1906: Stanford University and Environs (February 23 -- September 15, 2006) (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Earthquake: Brochure (2006) (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Earthquake: Case Maps (2006) (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Earthquake: Case Maps and Backdrops (2006) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Earthquake: Colors (2006) (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Earthquake: Guest Books (2006) (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Earthquake: Jon Carroll Visit (2006) (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Earthquake: Posters (2006) (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Earthquake: Publicity (2006) (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Earthquake: Reception (2006) (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Earthquake: Requests for exhibit banners and backdrops (2006) (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Earthquake: Text (2006) (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Charles Dickens and Show Biz (October 2, 2006 -- January 28, 2007) Exhibit Ad (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Dickens: Announcement (2006) (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Dickens: Banners -- Rotunda Mounting Instructions (2006) (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Dickens: Catalog (2006) (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Dickens: Catalog Cover (2006) (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Dickens: Catalog Display Copies (2006) (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Dickens: Catalog Flyers (2006) (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Dickens: Catalog Image Resolution Issues (2006) (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Dickens: Catalogue of items (2006) (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Dickens: Catalog single source drafts (2006) (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Dickens: Colors (2006) (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Dickens: Costume Case Removal (2006) (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Dickens: Costume Display (2006) (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Dickens: Dickens of Darkest England, 1986 (2006) (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Dickens: Hand-address lists for Dickens announcement (2006) (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Dickens: Jerry Kelly Correspondence (2006) (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Dickens: Large Print (2006) (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Dickens: Mailing List (2006) (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Dickens: Miller Type/Matthew Carter (2006) (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Dickens: Morgan-Stanley Reception, 11/16/06 (2006) (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Dickens: Object Labels and Case Texts (2006) (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Dickens: Opening Reception (2006) (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Dickens: Planning (2006) (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Dickens: Poster (2006) (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Dickens: Production Schedule (2006) (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Dickens: Publicity (2006) (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Dickens: Rotunda Banner (2006) (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Dickens: Scanning (2006) (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Dickens/Crawford Valuation, etc. (taken from binder) (2006) (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Dickens: Virtual Exhibition Gallery 1 of 2 (2006) (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Dickens: Virtual Exhibition Gallery 2 of 2 (2006) (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Dickens: Website (2006) (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - California Printers in the Fine Press Tradition 1975-2006: Selections from Stanford's Special Collections (February 12 -- June 17, 2007) Announcement and Poster (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Fine Press: Arts of the Book Poster (2007) (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Fine Press: Backdrops (2007) (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Fine Press: Binding and Paper Decorating (2007) (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Fine Press: Binding Text -- David's Comments (2007) (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Fine Press: Book Arts cases (2007) (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Fine Press: Booklists/winnowing process (2007) (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Fine Press: Case Maps (2007) (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Fine Press: Codex Foundation Statement (2007) (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Fine Press: Contact List (2007) (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Fine Press: Dennis Letbetters photos (2007) (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Fine Press: email correspondence (2007) (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Fine Press: images (2007) (Box 15, Folder 68)
  - Fine Press: Index (2007) (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Fine Press: Info Blanks (2007) (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Fine Press: Kathy Walkup's Suggestion (2007) (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Fine Press: Kudos and Correspondence (2007) (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Fine Press: Materials for Label Copy (2007) (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Fine Press: Misc. Correspondence (2007) (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Fine Press: Opening Party (2007) (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Fine Press: Outline (2007) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Fine Press: Paper Making (2007) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Fine Press: Paste Papers (2007) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Fine Press: PA Weekly (2007) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Fine Press: Planning Notes (2007) (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Fine Press: Press Release and Publicity (2007) (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Fine Press: Printing and Typography (2007) (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Fine Press: Production Schedule (2007) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Fine Press: Reading Copies (2007) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Fine Press: Reception Food (2007) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Fine Press: Reception Invitations and RSVPs (2007) (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Fine Press: Research Materials (2007) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Fine Press: RGT Intro (2007) (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Fine Press: Socrates Searches (2007) (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Fine Press: Susan King (2007) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Fine Press: Twinrocker Mould and Decker Loan (2007) (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Fine Press: Twinrocker Paper (2007) (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Fine Press: Xeroxed Texts (2007) (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - The Vico Collaborations: 1972|2003|2006 (July 2 -- December 2, 2007) Biographical Info (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Vico: Casemaps (2007) (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Vico: Constituency (2007) (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Vico: Cynthia Haven piece on Vico Exhibit (2007) (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Vico: Dennis and Jack Info (2007) (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Vico: Fun with Vico (2007) (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Vico: Info Sheets (2007) (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Vico: Jack Stauffacher (2007) (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Vico: Mailing List (2007) (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Vico: Planning Meeting 3/27/07 (2007) (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Vico: Meridien Type Samples (2007) (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Vico: Portfolio Measurements of Matting (2007) (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Vico: Postcard (2007) (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Vico: Press Release, Publicity (2007) (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Vico: Reception and Talk (2007) (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Vico: Sign (2007) (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Vico: Texts (2007) (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Vico: Texts -- edited (2007) (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Vico: Typographica Visit (2007) (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Vico: WEB Publicity (2007) (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Jack Stauffacher -- Exhibit 2 (not produced) (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Stauffacher Book Search (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Zuancho in Kyoto: Textile Design Books for the Kimono Trade (January 7 -- April 16, 2008) April and May Meeting Notes (2008) (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Zuancho: Articles (2008) (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Zuancho: Asian Art Museum Notes (2008) (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Zuancho: Azumagagami (2008) (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Zuancho: Banner Requests (2008) (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Zuancho: Calligraphy (2008) (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Zuancho: Case List (2008) (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Zuancho: Case 1 -- Kourin Gafu (2 vols.) (2008) (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Zuancho: Case 1 -- MM Bijutsu Sekai, on loan from Misako (2008) (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Zuancho: Case 1 -- MM Painting Album, on loan from Misako (2008) (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Zuancho: Case 1 -- Shin Zuan (2008) (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Zuancho: Case 2 -- Hanakagami (2008) (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Zuancho: Case 2 -- Hinagata (2008) (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Zuancho: Case 3 -- Tennen Hyaku Tsuru (2008) (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Zuancho: Case 3 -- Tennen Moyoukan, 5 vol. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Zuancho: Case 4 -- Kaiji/Kairo (2008) (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Zuancho: Case 4 -- Shima-Shima 2 vol. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Zuancho: Case 5 -- Hatou (2008) (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Zuancho: Case 6 -- Bunmei Furi (2008) (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Zuancho: Case 6 -- Keika Zuan 4 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Zuancho: Case 6 -- Matsuzukushi (2008) (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Zuancho: Case 6 -- Shin Bijutsukai 2 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Zuancho: Case 6 -- Takezukushi (2008) (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Zuancho: Case 7 -- Bijutsukai 7 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Zuancho: Case 7 -- Futaba Index Print (2008) (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Zuancho: Case 7 -- Kumo NoKagi (2008) (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Zuancho: Case 8 -- Tsuda Soifu, 1 of 2 (2008) (Box 16, Folder 67)
  - Zuancho: Case 8 -- Tsuda Soifu, 2 of 2 (2008) (Box 16, Folder 68)
  - Zuancho: Case 9 -- Kodai Moyou 6 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 69)
  - Zuancho: Case 9 -- Seiei (2008) (Box 16, Folder 70)
  - Zuancho: Case 10 -- Chinami 2 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 71)
  - Zuancho: Case 10? -- Kasuri Hyakushu 2 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 72)
  - Zuancho: Case 10 -- Senshoku Taikan 10 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 73)
  - Zuancho: Case 11 -- Shoukeikabekicho 2 vol. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 74)
  - Zuancho: Case 12 -- Jojou Hinagata 4 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 75)
  - Zuancho: Case 12 -- MM Hisui Kacho Zuan Shu (2008) (Box 16, Folder 76)
  - Zuancho: Case 12 -- Saikafu 2 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 77)
  - Zuancho: Case 12 -- Zuan Hyakudai 3 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 78)
  - Zuancho: Case 14 -- Seika 2 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 79)
  - Zuancho: Case 17 -- Kourin Moyou 2 vols. (2008) (Box 16, Folder 80)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Captions (2008) (Box 16, Folder 81)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Catalogs (2008) (Box 16, Folder 82)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Barcode (2008) (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Castle Press Quote (2008) (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Checklist (2008) (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Chicago Manual on Japanese Language Matters (2008) (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Color Graphics (2008) (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Cover Color Reference (2008) (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Cover Design Ideas (2008) (Box 16, Folder 89)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Distribution (2008) (Box 16, Folder 90)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Fact-checking (2008) (Box 16, Folder 91)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Illustration Selection (2008) (Box 16, Folder 92)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Japanese Copyright (2008) (Box 16, Folder 93)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Japanese Pattern Book Estimates (2008) (Box 16, Folder 94)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Kudos (2008) (Box 16, Folder 95)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Layout (2008) (Box 16, Folder 96)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Marnie's Edits (2008) (Box 16, Folder 97)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Mikio Matsuo Shoot (2008) (Box 16, Folder 98)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Misako's "Preface" (2008) (Box 16, Folder 99)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Notes to the Reader -- Zuancho Terminology Discussion (2008) (Box 16, Folder 100)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Pauline Ayumi Ota (2008) (Box 16, Folder 101)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Photoshoot List w/ Mikio Matsuo (2008) (Box 16, Folder 102)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Press Quote -- Stinehour (2008) (Box 16, Folder 103)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Pricing and Sales (2008) (Box 16, Folder 104)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Production (2008) (Box 16, Folder 105)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Proof -- Stinehour (2008) (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Proof -- blues -- Stinehour (2008) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Roberto's "Foreword" (2008) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Watermark Press Quote (2008) (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Zuancho: Catalog - Yokoya Essay -- edited versions (2008) (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Zuancho: Catalog - Yokoya Essay -- Edits/outline -- summer ‘07 (2008) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Zuancho: Catalog - Yokoya Essay -- Ken's Bibliography (2008) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Zuancho: Catalog - Yokoya Essay -- Ken Yokoya (2008) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Zuancho: Catalog - Yokoya Essay -- Ken Yokoya's Essay (2008) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Zuancho: Catalog - Yokoya Essay -- Letter to Ken Yokoya re: Editorial Changes (2008) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Zuancho: Catalog - Yokoya Essay -- Sent to Ken 9-14-07 (2008) (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Zuancho: Catalog - Yokoya Essay (2008) (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Zuancho: Catalog -- Yokoya Essay -- translation original (2008) (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Zuancho: Central Banner (2008) (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Zuancho: Coulter Construction Banner Installation (2008) (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Zuancho: Diane Mott/Textile Curator, De Young Museum (2008) (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Zuancho: Fine Arts Museum, Boston -- image search (2008) (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Zuancho: Freer and Sackler Image Search (2008) (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Zuancho: Haigyu Paper/Isao Nakamura, Exhibit at SF Craft and Folk Art Exhibit (2008) (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Zuancho: Hanafubuki (2008) (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Zuancho: Hanasekai (2008) (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Zuancho: Hinagatabon (2008) (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Zuancho: Images from Mitsui Memorial Museum (2008) (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Zuancho: Index of Zuancho PDF, "Index Print" by title (2008) (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Zuancho: Installation Photos (2008) (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Zuancho: Jan 17 RSVPs (2008) (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Zuancho: Japanese Books in SUL (2008) (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Zuancho: Japanese Pattern Books Reception (2008) (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Zuancho: Kansenzuroku (2008) (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Zuancho: Kimono Exhibit Event w/ ASUL (2008) (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Zuancho: Kimono Books exhibit timeline (2008) (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Zuancho: Kimono Book List (2008) (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Zuancho: The Kimono Painter: Kunihiko Moriguchi (2008) (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Zuancho: Kimono Pattern Book Purchase Notes (2008) (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Zuancho: Kimono-related book search (2008) (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Zuancho: Matsuo Image Inventory (2008) (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Zuancho: 12-15-06 Meeting notes (2008) (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Zuancho: Misako Conversation Notes (2008) (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Zuancho: Misako Mitsui Loan (2008) (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Zuancho: Misc. email correspondence (2008) (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Zuancho: MM Gafu Seitei, on loan from Misako Mitsui (2008) (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Zuancho: MM Issotei, on loan from Misako Mitsui (2008) (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Zuancho: Museum of Fine Arts/ Boston, List of Hinagabaton/Kimono Pattern Books (2008) (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Zuancho: National Anthro Archives Request for Image and repro. Permission (2008) (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Zuancho: National Museum of Nat. History Japanese Textile Image Search (2008) (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Zuancho: Notes (2008) (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Zuancho: NYPL Image Search (2008) (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Zuancho: Pattern Book Interview Questions (2008) (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Zuancho: PA Weekly/Kevin Kirby (2008) (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Zuancho: PDF Duplicates (2008) (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Zuancho: Postcard (2008) (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Zuancho: Press Release Copies (2008) (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Zuancho: Publicity (2008) (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Zuancho: Publicity -- contacts mailing list (2008) (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Zuancho: Readings re: Japanese Textiles (2008) (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Zuancho: reception invitation mailing (2008) (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Zuancho: Reiko Yoshimuva (Freer and Sackler) (2008) (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Zuancho: Shiki No Hana, 10 vols. (2008) (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Zuancho: Surface Design Association, publicity (2008) (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Zuancho: Textile Exhibits (2008) (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Zuancho: The Textile Museum brochures (2008) (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Zuancho: The Textile Museum, Washington, D.C. (2008) (Box 17, Folder 62)